We are establishing a task force for the Kira case.
キラ事件の捜査本部を設置する。
The Commissioner General has issued orders to treat this case as the highest priority.
警察庁長官より、この事件を最優先事項として扱うよう指示が出ている。
Those who participate in the investigation must be prepared to risk their lives.
捜査に参加する者は、命の危険を覚悟してほしい。
According to L's analysis, Kira resides in the Kanto region and is most likely a student or a working professional.
Lの分析によれば、キラは関東地方在住で、 学生もしくは社会人の可能性が高い。
There is a pattern in the times of death of the criminals. On weekdays, deaths occur after the evening. On weekends, they are irregular.
犯罪者の死亡時刻に規則性がある。 平日は夕方以降、週末は不規則だ。
In other words, Kira has other activities during the day. Most likely school or work.
つまり、キラには日中に別の活動がある。 学校か仕事だろう。
Analysis of the killing method is also progressing. Kira requires both a name and a face.
殺害方法についても分析が進んでいる。 キラは名前と顔の両方を必要としている。
Since only criminals who have been covered by the media have died, it is believed that Kira obtains information through media sources.
報道された犯罪者のみが死亡していることから、 キラはメディアを通じて情報を得ていると考えられる。
The personal information of investigators must be strictly managed. If our names are leaked, we too could become targets.
捜査員の個人情報は厳重に管理する必要がある。 名前が漏れれば、我々も標的になりかねない。
A message from L: "Anyone who may come into contact with Kira must never reveal their real name."
Lからの伝言だ。「キラに接触する可能性のある者は、 絶対に本名を明かすな。」
Father, are you involved in the Kira investigation?
父さん、キラ事件の捜査に関わっているのか？
Light, I cannot tell you anything about this matter. It is for our family's safety.
月、この件については何も話せない。 家族の安全のためだ。
I understand. I believe that you are doing the right thing, Father.
わかっている。父さんが正しいことをしていると信じている。
The further the investigation progresses, the closer they get to me. But this is within my expectations.
捜査が進むほど、僕に近づいてくる。 だが、それは想定の範囲内だ。
The fact that my father is in the Kira task force means I can keep track of the investigation's progress.
父がキラ対策本部にいるということは、 捜査の進捗を把握できるということだ。
I will acknowledge L's deductive abilities. But without evidence, he cannot catch me.
Lの推理力は認めよう。 だが、証拠がなければ僕を捕まえることはできない。
As long as no one knows this notebook exists, it is impossible to uncover Kira's true identity.
このノートの存在を知らない限り、 キラの正体にたどり着くことは不可能だ。
Continue your investigation, L. The closer you get, the deeper you fall into my trap.
捜査を続けるがいい、L。 お前が近づけば近づくほど、僕の罠に嵌まるだけだ。
Everything is going according to plan.
全ては計画通りだ。
In this battle of wits, I will be the one who laughs last.
この知能戦、最後に笑うのは僕だ。